<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="couldntFindDesc">Can\'t find description</string>
    <string name="harryPotterDesc"><b>Harry Potter and the Sorcerer\'s Stone (2001)</b>\n\n
        Harry Potter has lived under the stairs at his aunt and uncle\' s house his whole life.
        But on his 11th birthday, he learns he\'s a powerful wizard — with a place waiting for him
        at the Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. As he learns to harness his newfound
        powers with the help of the school\'s kindly headmaster, Harry uncovers the truth
        about his parents\' deaths — and about the villain who\'s to blame.
    </string>
    <string name="sweeneyToddDesc"><b>Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street (2007)</b>\n\n
        The story is about Sweeney Todd, who was first named Benjamin Barker. Todd comes back from
        the prison camps in Australia, where he was for fifteen years. Then he learns from the pie-maker
        Mrs. Lovett that his wife poisoned herself after being raped by Judge Turpin. He also finds
        out that the Judge is keeping his daughter. Todd decides to take revenge. Sweeney and Mrs Lovett
        become partners in a plan that ends in murder, business for Lovett\' s pie shop, and a lot of sadness.
    </string>
    <string name="dogsPurposeDesc"><b>A Dog\'s Purpose (2017)</b>\n\n
        In the world there are many different breeds of dogs, and all of them, regardless of size
        and suit, are loyal and devoted friends of their master. Every day they are waiting for your
        return home and are ready to fulfill all your commands to which you have trained them. The plot
        of the film revolves around a dog named Bailey, whose soul goes on an amazing journey around
        the world, replacing cities and hosts. Every time this dog lives a bright and rich life next
        to his beloved masters who take care of him in every possible way. He is waiting for a lot of
        exciting adventures with completely different people, but so far he has someone to wait, lick
        and with whom to play, his dog\'s life is filled with meaning…
    </string>
    <string name="ageOfAdalineDesc"><b>The Age of Adaline (2015)</b>\n\n
        Adaline Bowman was born on January 1, 1908. She was no different from the rest of the people,
        but in the winter of 1935 her life changed forever. She got into a car accident, after which
        something incredible happened to her. From that very night she became timeless and did not age
        for a single day. However, this gift was a real test for her, because all her close relatives
        were aging, which caused her great pain. Despite her long life, she could not become a happy
        woman and find her true love. But one day in her life there is a man for whose sake she can
        again become mortal, to grow old beside him…
    </string>

    <string name="theAvengersDesc"><b>The Avengers (2012)</b>\n\n
        Earth\'s mightiest heroes must come together and learn to fight as a team if they are going to
        stop the mischievous Loki and his alien army from enslaving humanity.
    </string>
    <string name="morningGloryDesc"><b>Morning Glory (2010)</b>\n\n
        When hard-working TV producer Becky Fuller is fired from a local news program, her career begins
        to look as bleak as her hapless love life. Stumbling into a job at “Daybreak” (the last-place
        national morning news show), Becky decides to revitalize the show by bringing on legendary TV
        anchor Mike Pomeroy. Unfortunately, Pomeroy refuses to cover morning show staples like celebrity
        gossip, weather, fashion and crafts, let alone work with his new co-host, Colleen Peck, a former
        beauty queen and longtime morning show personality, who is more than happy covering morning “news.”
        As Mike and Colleen clash, first behind the scenes and then on the air, Becky\`s blossoming love
        affair with fellow producer, Adam Bennett begins to unravel. And soon Becky is struggling to save
        her relationship, her reputation, her job and ultimately, the show.
    </string>
    <string name="theLordOfTheRings1Desc"><b>The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring (2001)</b>\n\n
        J.R.R. Tolkien\`s fantasy world of Middle Earth comes to life in the first of three films telling
        the adventurous tale of one small group’s journey to turn back the overwhelming tide of evil threatening the world.
        Fans and newcomers to the fiction are given a brief introduction to the One Ring, its making, its
        evil power and its discovery by the hobbit Bilbo Baggins. Bilbo disappears, leaving the ring to
        his nephew, young Frodo Baggins. Bilbo’s friend, the wizard Gandalf, discovers the true secret
        of the ring and starts Frodo on his eventful journey to destroy the evil-filled charm.
        The fellowship is forged as Frodo is helped on his journey by three hobbit companions, Gandalf
        and representatives of the elves, dwarves and men. But the spirit of the ring’s evil maker seeks
        its power, to once more rule the earth. Despite its three-hour length, the visually stunning film
        and enthralling adventure will capture audiences with its tale of bravery and friendship.
    </string>
    <string name="klausDesc"><b>Klaus (2019)</b>\n\n
        A simple act of kindness always sparks another, even in a frozen, faraway place. When Smeerensburg\'s
        new postman, Jesper, befriends toymaker Klaus, their gifts melt an age-old feud and deliver a
        sleigh full of holiday traditions.
    </string>
    <string name="treasurePlanetDesc"><b>Treasure Planet (2002)</b>\n\n
        When the alien Billy Bones crashes near the Benbow Inn, where Jim’s mother works as a waitress,
        he gives a golden orb with a special star map to Jim for safekeeping. Jim’s astro-physicist friend,
        Dr. Doppler, recognizes it as a treasure map that could lead to Flint’s hidden fortune. They hire
        the starship RLS Legacy, helmed by the feline-like Captain Amelia. Among the crew is John Silver,
        a cyborg – part man, part machine – and his pet ‘Morph’ who can change shapes.
    </string>
    <string name="theNightmareBeforeChristmasDesc"><b>The Nightmare Before Christmas (1993)</b>\n\n
        Jack Skellington, king of Halloween Town, discovers Christmas Town, but his attempts to bring Christmas to his home causes confusion.
    </string>
    <string name="cocoDesc"><b>Coco (2017)</b>\n\n
        Aspiring musician Miguel, confronted with his family\'s ancestral ban on music, enters the
        Land of the Dead to find his great-great-grandfather, a legendary singer.
    </string>
</resources>