<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="couldntFindDesc">Can\'t find description</string>
    <string name="harryPotterDesc"><b>Harry Potter and the Sorcerer\'s Stone (2001)</b>\n\n
        Harry Potter has lived under the stairs at his aunt and uncle\' s house his whole life.
        But on his 11th birthday, he learns he\'s a powerful wizard — with a place waiting for him
        at the Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. As he learns to harness his newfound
        powers with the help of the school\'s kindly headmaster, Harry uncovers the truth
        about his parents\' deaths — and about the villain who\'s to blame.
    </string>
    <string name="sweeneyToddDesc"><b>Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street (2007)</b>\n\n
        The story is about Sweeney Todd, who was first named Benjamin Barker. Todd comes back from
        the prison camps in Australia, where he was for fifteen years. Then he learns from the pie-maker
        Mrs. Lovett that his wife poisoned herself after being raped by Judge Turpin. He also finds
        out that the Judge is keeping his daughter. Todd decides to take revenge. Sweeney and Mrs Lovett
        become partners in a plan that ends in murder, business for Lovett\' s pie shop, and a lot of sadness.
    </string>
    <string name="dogsPurposeDesc"><b>A Dog\'s Purpose (2017)</b>\n\n
        In the world there are many different breeds of dogs, and all of them, regardless of size
        and suit, are loyal and devoted friends of their master. Every day they are waiting for your
        return home and are ready to fulfill all your commands to which you have trained them. The plot
        of the film revolves around a dog named Bailey, whose soul goes on an amazing journey around
        the world, replacing cities and hosts. Every time this dog lives a bright and rich life next
        to his beloved masters who take care of him in every possible way. He is waiting for a lot of
        exciting adventures with completely different people, but so far he has someone to wait, lick
        and with whom to play, his dog\'s life is filled with meaning…
    </string>
    <string name="ageOfAdalineDesc"><b>The Age of Adaline (2015)</b>\n\n
        Adaline Bowman was born on January 1, 1908. She was no different from the rest of the people,
        but in the winter of 1935 her life changed forever. She got into a car accident, after which
        something incredible happened to her. From that very night she became timeless and did not age
        for a single day. However, this gift was a real test for her, because all her close relatives
        were aging, which caused her great pain. Despite her long life, she could not become a happy
        woman and find her true love. But one day in her life there is a man for whose sake she can
        again become mortal, to grow old beside him…
    </string>
</resources>